<hockeyPlayers>

<player id="0">
<jersey>00</jersey>
<name>John Davidson</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>While his hockey career was fraught with many significant injuries, he is perhaps best remembered for leading the Rangers to the 1979 Stanley Cup Finals on an injured left knee.</p><p>Davidson was the first, and one of only two, NHL players to wear the number 00; after Martin Biron briefly wore the number in 1995, the league banned the use of the number.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/00_john_davidson.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Davidson_(ice_hockey)</link>
</player>

<player id="1">
<jersey>1</jersey>
<name>Terry Sawchuk</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Sawchuck played 21 seasons in the National Hockey League for the Detroit Red Wings, Boston Bruins, Toronto Maple Leafs, Los Angeles Kings and New York Rangers between 1949-1970.</p><p>He finished his hockey career with 447 wins, a record that stood for thirty years, and his career record of 103 shutouts remained unsurpassed among NHL goaltenders, until <a style="color:blue" onclick="getPlayer('30')" href=#><b>Martin Brodeur</b></a> bested that mark on December 21, 2009.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/01_terry_sawchuk.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Terry_Sawchuk</link>
</player>

<player id="2">
<jersey>2</jersey>
<name>Doug Harvey</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Harvey played in the National Hockey League from 1947 until 1964, and from 1966 until 1969. He is widely regarded as one of the greatest defencemen to ever play the game, winning the James Norris Memorial Trophy as the league's top defenceman on seven occasions.</p><p>In an era when the defenceman's role did not include scoring points, Harvey used his skating speed and passing ability to become a factor in making the Canadiens a high-scoring team.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/02_doug_harvey.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Doug_Harvey_(ice_hockey)</link>
</player>

<player id="3">
<jersey>3</jersey>
<name>Pierre Pilote</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Pilote was a three-time recipient of the Norris Trophy as outstanding defenceman in 1963, 1964, and 1965 as well as runner-up in 1962, 1966 and 1967.</p><p>He was on the first or second all-star team every year from 1960 to 1967. During his playing career, he was respected as an iron man playing 376 consecutive games.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/03_pierre_pilote.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pierre_Pilote</link>
</player>

<player id="4">
<jersey>4</jersey>
<name>Bobby Orr</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Orr inspired the game of hockey with his command of the two-way game. While a few Hall of Fame defencemen were known for having offensive ability, they were the exception rather than the norm in the NHL before Orr's arrival.</p><p>Orr's offensive style has influenced countless defencemen who followed him. His speed – most notably a rapid acceleration – and his open-ice artistry electrified fans as he set almost every conceivable record for a defenceman.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/04_bobby_orr.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bobby_Orr</link>
</player>

<player id="5">
<jersey>5</jersey>
<name>Nicklas Lidström</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Over his 20 NHL seasons, Lidström won four Stanley Cups, seven James Norris Memorial Trophies as the NHL's top defensive player, one Conn Smythe Trophy as the playoff MVP, and has been voted into twelve NHL All-Star Games.</p><p>Over the course of his career, Lidström became the first European-born and trained NHL captain to win the Stanley Cup, as well as the first European player named playoff MVP.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/05_nicklas_lidstrom.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nicklas_Lidstr%C3%B6m</link>
</player>

<player id="6">
<jersey>6</jersey>
<name>Ace Bailey</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Bailey's #6 jersey was the first ever to be retired by an NHL team, and is one of only two to have been permanently retired by the Maple Leafs (the other being Bill Barilko's #5).</p><p>He was the leading scorer and goal scorer in the NHL in the 1928–29 season, with 22 goals and 32 points in 44 games. He was again the Leafs' leading scorer in 1929–30 and one point short of repeating in 1930–31. Bailey was inducted into the Hockey Hall of Fame in 1975.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/06_ace_bailey.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ace_Bailey</link>
</player>

<player id="7">
<jersey>7</jersey>
<name>Phil Esposito</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>A member of the Hockey Hall of Fame, he played 18 seasons in the National Hockey League for the Chicago Black Hawks, Boston Bruins and New York Rangers. He is considered one of the best to have ever played in the NHL, and is the older brother of fellow Hall-of-Famer <a style="color:blue" onclick="getPlayer('35')" href=#><b>Tony Esposito</b></a>, a goaltender.</p><p>Esposito was elected to the Hockey Hall of Fame in 1984. In December 1987, his #7 jersey was retired by the Boston Bruins in an emotional ceremony where the then-current wearer, superstar defenseman <a style="color:blue" onclick="getPlayer('77')" href=#><b>Ray Bourque</b></a>, pulled off his #7 jersey to reveal his new number, 77 — dramatically surrendering his old number in Esposito's favor.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/07_phil_esposito.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Phil_Esposito</link>
</player>

<player id="8">
<jersey>8</jersey>
<name>Alexander Ovechkin</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>During the 2007–08 season, he led the NHL with 65 goals and 112 points to capture the Rocket Richard and Art Ross Trophies. That season he also won the Lester B. Pearson Award as the top player voted by the NHL Players' Association and the Hart Memorial Trophy as the league's MVP.</p><p>He is the only player to win all four awards since the Rocket Richard Trophy's inception in 1999.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/08_alexander_ovechkin.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ovechkin</link>
</player>

<player id="9">
<jersey>9</jersey>
<name>Gordie Howe</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Howe is most famous for his scoring prowess, physical strength, and career longevity. He is the only player to have competed in the NHL in five different decades (1940s through 1980s).<p></p>A four-time Stanley Cup champion with the Red Wings, he won six Hart Trophies as the league's most valuable player and six Art Ross Trophies as the leading scorer. He was the inaugural recipient of the NHL Lifetime Achievement Award in 2008.</p><p>Howe's name and nickname, "Mr. Hockey," as well as his wife's nickname as "Mrs. Hockey," are registered trademarks.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/09_gordie_howe.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gordie_Howe</link>
</player>

<player id="10">
<jersey>10</jersey>
<name>Ron Fracis</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Francis played almost ten seasons with the Whalers, serving as captain for almost six and setting nearly every offensive record in franchise history. He was traded to the Pittsburgh Penguins on March 4, 1991, where he centred a formidable second line behind Mario Lemieux, as the Penguins won their first Stanley Cup less than three months later.</p><p>He won 2 Stanley Cups, in 1990–91 and the following season, with the Pittsburgh Penguins. His best season was 1995–96 when he had 119 points; that season, he led the league in assists with 92. The previous season, he had not only led the league in assists with 48 over the strike-shortened half-season schedule, but became the first player to win both the Frank J. Selke Trophy and the Lady Byng Trophy in the same season.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/10_ron_francis.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ron_Francis</link>
</player>

<player id="11">
<jersey>11</jersey>
<name>Mark Messier</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Mark Messier spent a quarter of a century in the NHL (1979-2004) with the Edmonton Oilers, New York Rangers, and Vancouver Canucks. Messier is considered one of the greatest NHL players of all time without an Olympic medal. He is second on the all-time career lists for regular season points (1887), playoff points (295) and regular season games played (1756). </p><p> He won six Stanley Cups, five with the Oilers and one with the Rangers, and is the only player to captain two different professional teams to championships. His playoff leadership while in New York, which ended a 54-year Stanley Cup drought in 1994, earned him the nickname "The Messiah". He was also known, over the course of his career, as "The Moose" for his aggression and strength. In 2007, he was inducted into the Hockey Hall of Fame, in his first year of eligibility.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/11_mark_messier.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mark_Messier</link>
</player>

<player id="12">
<jersey>12</jersey>
<name>Jarome Iginla</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Jarome Iginla was a member of the Calgary Flames between 1996 and 2013 where he served as captain for nine seasons and played briefly with the Pittsburgh Penguins in 2012-2013 before joining the Boston Bruins in 2013-2014.</p><p>He led the NHL in goals and points in 2001-2002, and won the Lester B. Pearson Award as its most valuable player as voted by the players. In 2003-2004, Iginla led the league in goals for the second time and captained the Flames to the Stanley Cup Finals, leading the league in playoff scoring.</p><p>Iginla scored 50 goals in a season on two occasions and is one of seven players in NHL history to score 30 goals in 11 consecutive seasons. He has scored 565 goals and 1,315 points in his career and has been recognized by the league for donating $2,000 to children's charity for every goal he scored.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/12_jarome_iginla.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jarome_Iginla</link>
</player>

<player id="13">
<jersey>13</jersey>
<name>Mats Sundin</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Mats Sundin was originally drafted first overall in 1989 by the Quebec Nordiques, but was later traded to the Toronto Maple Leafs in 1994, where he played the majority of his career, serving 11 seasons as team captain. At the end of the 2007-08 NHL season, Sundin had been the longest serving non-North American born captain in NHL history.</p><p>He is the Leafs' franchise all-time leader in goals (420) and points (984). Over his career, Sundin averaged just over a point per game (1349 points in 1346 NHL games). Internationally, Sundin won three gold medals with Sweden at the World Championships and a gold medal at the 2006 Winter Olympics in Turin. Sundin was elected to the Hockey Hall of Fame on June 26, 2012.</p> ]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/13_mats_sundin.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mats_Sundin</link>
</player>

<player id="14">
<jersey>14</jersey>
<name>Brendan Shanahan</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>With his physical play and goal scoring ability, Shanahan scored 656 goals in his NHL career spanning over 1,500 NHL games and, at the time of his retirement, was the leader among active NHL players for goals scored. Shanahan is the only player in NHL history with over 600 goals and 2,000 penalty minutes.</p><p>While playing with the Red Wings, he won three Stanley Cup championships. Shanahan won a gold medal at the 1994 World Championships, 2002 Winter Olympics, and a 1991 Canada Cup championship. Having won what are considered the three most prominent team titles in ice hockey, Shanahan is a member of the elite Triple Gold Club. Shanahan was elected to the Hockey Hall of Fame on July 9, 2013.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/14_brendan_shanahan.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brendan_Shanahan</link>
</player>

<player id="15">
<jersey>15</jersey>
<name>Milt Schmidt</name>
<bio><![CDATA[Schmidt was a key ingredient to the Bruins' success as they rampaged to a hard fought Stanley Cup victory in 1939. The following season would be Schmidt's true coming out party, as he led the league in scoring and guided the Bruins to another first place finish and the third most goals in team history to date. The 1941 season saw Schmidt spearhead the Bruins to their second Cup win in three years.</p><p> He was named captain for the Bruins in 1951 and won the Hart Trophy as the league's most valuable player that year. He is an Honoured Member of the Hockey Hall of Fame.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/15_milt_schmidt.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Milt_Schmidt</link>
</player>

<player id="16">
<jersey>16</jersey>
<name>Brett Hull</name>
<bio><![CDATA[Hull's career total of 741 goals is the third highest in NHL history, and he is one of five players to score 50 goals in 50 games. His championship winning goal for Dallas in overtime of game six of the 1999 Stanley Cup Finals is one of the most controversial in league history and remains the focus of debate (over whether it was scored within the rules of the time).</p><p>His 86 goals in 1990-1991 is the third highest single-season total in NHL history. Hull won the Hart Memorial Trophy and Lester B. Pearson Award that year as the league's most valuable player.</p><p>Hull was inducted into the Hockey Hall of Fame in 2009, joining his father Bobby to become the first father-and-son pair of players in the Hall. They are the only pair to each score 1,000 career points in the NHL. Hull's nickname, "the Golden Brett" is a reference to his father's nickname of "the Golden Jet".]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/16_brett_hull.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brett_Hull</link>
</player>

<player id="17">
<jersey>17</jersey>
<name>Jari Kurri</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Kurri teamed up with <a style="color:blue" onclick="getPlayer('99')" href=#><b>Wayne Gretzky</b></a> during his first year in the NHL and they became one of the most prolific scoring tandems ever to play in the NHL. Gretzky assisted on 364 of Kurri's 601 career goals, while the "Finnish Flash" had an assist on 196 Gretzky goals. Kurri won five Stanley Cups, all with Edmonton (1984, 1985, 1987, 1988, and 1990).</p><p>In 1984Ð85 he had 135 points and scored 50 goals in his first 50 games. A year later, he led the league in goals with 68. In the 1985-playoffs he scored 19 goals (18 games) included four hat tricks, a still-standing record in a playoff season. Kurri scored three of the hat tricks against the Blackhawks in the conference finals, also a feat that no player has ever equaled. He was inducted into the Hockey Hall of Fame in 2001.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/17_jari_kurri.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jari_Kurri</link>
</player>

<player id="18">
<jersey>18</jersey>
<name>Denis Savard</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Savard began his career during the 1980–81 NHL season in which he had three assists in his first game. He then went on to set the Blackhawks' record (since broken) for most points by a rookie with 75.</p><p>In 1,196 NHL games, Savard scored 473 goals and 865 assists, totalling 1338 points. He trails only Bobby Hull and Stan Mikita for total points in Chicago Blackhawks history.</p><p>On March 19, 1998, the Blackhawks retired his jersey number #18. Savard was inducted into the Hockey Hall of Fame on November 13, 2000.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/18_denis_savard.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Denis_Savard</link>
</player>

<player id="19">
<jersey>19</jersey>
<name>Steve Yzerman</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Prior to the 1986–87 season at the age of 21, Yzerman was named captain of the Red Wings and continuously served for the next two decades (dressing as captain for over 1300 games), retiring as the longest-serving captain of any team in North American major league sports history.</p><p>Yzerman won numerous awards during his career, including the Lester B. Pearson Award in 1988–89, the Conn Smythe Trophy in 1998, the Selke Trophy in 2000, and the Bill Masterton Memorial Trophy in 2003. He was a ten-time NHL All-Star, a First Team All-Star in 2000, and a member of the All-Rookie Team in 1984.</p><p>Yzerman's #19 jersey was officially retired on January 2, 2007 and he was inducted in the Hockey Hall of Fame in 2009, his first year of eligibility.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/19_steve_yzerman.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Steve_Yzerman</link>
</player>

<player id="20">
<jersey>20</jersey>
<name>Luc Robitaille</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Robitaille scored more than 40 goals in each of his first eight seasons, including three 50 or more goal seasons, with a career-high 63 in 1992–93.</p><p>At the end of his career, Robitaille had made eight All-Star teams and set the NHL record for goals and points by a left winger. He set the Kings’ franchise record for goals, finished second in games played, fourth in assists, and second in points.</p><p>Robitaille retired after the 2005–06 season as the highest-scoring left winger in NHL history.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/20_luc_robitaille.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Luc_Robitaille</link>
</player>

<player id="21">
<jersey>21</jersey>
<name>Peter Forsberg</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Known for his on-ice vision and physical play, Forsberg is considered one of the most complete players of his generation. His 19-year professional career includes 13 years in the National Hockey League, where he won two Stanley Cups with the Colorado Avalanche, as well as several individual honors including the Hart Memorial Trophy in 2003.</p><p>He won four gold medals with Sweden in his career; the 1992 and 1998 World Championships and the 1994 and 2006 Winter Olympics. Combined with his two Stanley Cup championships, he is a member of the Triple Gold Club and the only Swede who has won each of the three competitions twice. Forsberg was inducted in the IIHF Hall of Fame in 2013.</p><p>As of 2012, he stands ninth all-time in career points-per-game and fourth all-time in career assists-per-game in the NHL, only behind <a style="color:blue" onclick="getPlayer('99')" href=#><b>Wayne Gretzky</b></a>, <a style="color:blue" onclick="getPlayer('66')" href=#><b>Mario Lemieux</b></a> and <a style="color:blue" onclick="getPlayer('4')" href=#><b>Bobby Orr</b></a>.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/21_peter_forsberg.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peter_Forsberg</link>
</player>

<player id="22">
<jersey>22</jersey>
<name>Mike Bossy</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Bossy is the only player in NHL history to score consecutive Stanley Cup winning goals, in 1982 and 1983, and is the NHL's all-team leader in average goals scored per regular season game. He played for the New York Islanders for his entire career and was a crucial part of their four-year reign as Stanley Cup champions in the early 1980s.</p><p>As of 2011, he held the record for most consecutive 50+ goal seasons (9), most 60+ goal seasons (5) (tied with Wayne Gretzky) and highest goals-per-game average (.762 goals per game), among other records.</p><p>Bossy was inducted into the Hockey Hall of Fame in 1991 and his #22 jersey was retired by the Islanders on March 3, 1992.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/22_mike_bossy.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mike_Bossy</link>
</player>

<player id="23">
<jersey>23</jersey>
<name>Bob Gainey</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>A defensive specialist, Gainey played with the Montreal Canadiens from 1973–74 to 1988–89, winning four consecutive Frank J. Selke Trophies, awarded to the league's best defensive forward and four consecutive Stanley Cups from 1976 to 1979.</p><p>In total, Bob Gainey played in 1160 regular season games, scored 239 goals, and registered 263 assists. He was elected to the Hockey Hall of Fame in 1992.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/23_bob_gainey.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bob_Gainey</link>
</player>

<player id="24">
<jersey>24</jersey>
<name>Chris Chelios</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Chelios currently holds the record for most games played in the NHL by a defenseman and is fifth overall with 1,651, and is tied with <a style="color:blue" onclick="getPlayer('9')" href=#><b>Gordie Howe</b></a> for most NHL seasons played with 26.</p><p>In the 2008–09 season, he appeared in the playoffs for an NHL record 24th time, having missed the playoffs only twice (1997–98 and 2009–10) in his entire career. Chelios was elected to the Hockey Hall of Fame on July 9, 2013.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/24_chris_chelios.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chris_Chelios</link>
</player>

<player id="25">
<jersey>25</jersey>
<name>Dave Andreychuk</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Andreychuk is one of the highest scoring left wingers in NHL history, and is the league's all-time leader in power-play goals with 274. He was drafted by the Buffalo Sabres in 1982 and went on to play 11 seasons in Buffalo.</p><p>In the 2001–02 NHL season, Andreychuk made a shocking move which would pay dividends in the long run. Rather than sign with a Stanley Cup contender, he signed with the lowly Tampa Bay Lightning, to which he was able to bring some much-needed veteran leadership.</p><p>The Lightning again missed the playoffs that season, and Andreychuk refused trades to contenders, stating his work with the team was not finished. Qualifying for the playoffs for a second consecutive year, Andreychuk helped the Lightning defeat the Calgary Flames in seven games to win the Stanley Cup for the first time in franchise history.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/25_dave_andreychuk.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dave_Andreychuk</link>
</player>

<player id="26">
<jersey>26</jersey>
<name>Peter Šťastný</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>When the startling news broke in 1980 that Czechoslovakia player of the year, Peter Šťastný, and his brother Anton, had defected to Canada to play with the Quebec Nordiques, it represented a watershed moment in professional hockey as one of the first major stars of Eastern bloc hockey to join the NHL.</p><p>Šťastný was one of four players to record 1000 or more points in the decade of the 1980s (1059). Previously, only <a style="color:blue" onclick="getPlayer('7')" href=#><b>Phil Esposito</b></a> had topped 1000 points in one decade, and only <a style="color:blue" onclick="getPlayer('99')" href=#><b>Gretzky</b></a> outscored Šťastný in the 1980s decade.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/26_peter_stastny.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peter_Stastny</link>
</player>

<player id="27">
<jersey>27</jersey>
<name>Scott Niedermayer</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Niedermayer is a four-time Stanley Cup champion and played in five NHL All-Star Games. He won the James Norris Memorial Trophy in 2003–04 as the NHL's top defenceman and the Conn Smythe Trophy in 2007 as the most valuable player of the playoffs.</p><p>He is a member of the Triple Gold Club, signifying he has won the Stanley Cup, the World Championship and an Olympic gold medal. Having also won the World Junior Championship and the World Cup of Hockey, makes him the only player in history to win every major North American and international championship available to a Canadian player.</p><p>Regarded as one of the greatest defencemen in NHL history, Niedermayer has earned numerous accolades throughout his career. He was inducted into Canada's Sports Hall of Fame in 2012 and into the Hockey Hall of Fame in November 2013. The New Jersey Devils and Kamloops Blazers have both retired his uniform number.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/27_scott_niedermayer.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scott_Niedermayer</link>
</player>

<player id="28">
<jersey>28</jersey>
<name>Steve Larmer</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>From 1982–1993, Larmer played in 884 consecutive games for the Blackhawks, an NHL record for most consecutive games played with the same team, and the third longest consecutive-games streak in league history. He won the 1983 Calder Memorial Trophy as well as being named to the NHL All-Rookie Team that year.</p><p>Larmer was a member of the 1991 Canada Cup team for Canada, where he led the entire competition in goals (6) and ranked second in points (11) behind only <a style="color:blue" onclick="getPlayer('99')" href=#><b>Wayne Gretzky</b></a>.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/28_steve_larmer.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Steve_Larmer</link>
</player>

<player id="29">
<jersey>29</jersey>
<name>Ken Dryden</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Dryden made his NHL debut in 1971 for the Canadiens, playing only six regular-season games after a late-season call-up but sporting a minuscule 1.65 goals-against average. The Canadiens went on to win the Stanley cup, with Dryden as the no 1 goalie ahead of veteran All-Star Rogie Vachon. Dryden also won the Conn Smythe Trophy as the playoffs' most valuable player that year.</p><p>He won the Calder Memorial Trophy in 1972 as the Rookie of the year because the previous year he did not play enough regular season games to become eligible. He remains the only NHL player to ever win the Conn Smythe Trophy before winning the rookie of the year award.</p><p>Dryden was the backbone of 5 more Stanley Cup-winning teams in 1973, 1976, 1977, 1978, and 1979. His #29 was retired by the Canadiens on January 29, 2007.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/29_ken_dryden.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ken_Dryden</link>
</player>

<player id="30">
<jersey>30</jersey>
<name>Martin Brodeur</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Brodeur is the NHL's all-time leader in regular season wins (surpassing <a style="color:blue" onclick="getPlayer('33')" href=#><b>Patrick Roy</b></a> in 2009), losses, shutouts, and games played, and holds numerous other league and franchise records.</p><p>He is the only goalie in NHL history with eight 40-win seasons. He is a four-time Vezina Trophy winner, a five-time Jennings Trophy winner, a ten-time NHL All-Star, a Calder Memorial Trophy winner, and one of only two NHL goaltenders to score a goal in both the regular season and the playoffs.</p><p>In his 21-year tenure with the Devils, he has won three Stanley Cup championships and has been in the playoffs every year but three. Brodeur has won two Olympic gold medals with Team Canada in the 2002 and 2010 Winter Olympic Games.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/30_martin_brodeur.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Martin_Brodeur</link>
</player>

<player id="31">
<jersey>31</jersey>
<name>Billy Smith</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>On November 28, 1979 Smith became the first NHL goaltender to be credited with scoring a goal, in a game between the New York Islanders and the Colorado Rockies.</p><p>In the first game of the 1983 Stanley Cup finals the Islanders won 2-0 against the Edmonton Oilers, and Smith shut out the likes of Mark Messier, Wayne Gretzky, Jari Kurri, and Paul Coffey. The Islanders won in 4 games, with Smith allowing the Oilers only 6 goals and winning the Conn Smythe Trophy as Most Valuable Player in the Playoffs.</p><p>Smith helped the Islanders win four straight Stanley Cups (1980–83), reach the finals five straight times (1980–84), and win a record 19 consecutive playoff series from 1980–84.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/31_billy_smith.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Billy_Smith_(ice_hockey)</link>
</player>

<player id="32">
<jersey>32</jersey>
<name>Dale Hunter</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>With amassing a staggering 3565 penalty minutes, Hunter currently has the second-most penalty minutes in NHL history.</p><p>Even though Hunter was nicknamed the "Nuisance" on ice (La Petite Peste in French), he was known to be humble in the dressing room and a sort of gentleman. He was the "perfect player", always the first to arrive at practice and ready to do all his best for the team.</p><p>Thanks to his charisma, Hunter was a fan favourite in both Quebec and Washington, where he played 7 and 12 seasons, respectively.</p><p>The Capitals retired Hunter's #32 jersey in 2000.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/32_dale_hunter.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dale_Hunter</link>
</player>

<player id="33">
<jersey>33</jersey>
<name>Patrick Roy</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Nicknamed "Saint Patrick," Roy split his professional career between the Montreal Canadiens, whom he played with for 10 years, and the Colorado Avalanche, whom he played with for 8 years, both of the NHL. Roy won four Stanley Cups during his career, two with each franchise.</p><p>In 2004, Roy was selected as the greatest goaltender in NHL history by a panel of 41 writers, coupled with a simultaneous fan poll. On November 13, 2006, Roy was inducted into the Hockey Hall of Fame. He is the only player in NHL history to win the Conn Smythe Trophy three times, in different decades, and for two different teams. Roy's No. 33 jersey is retired by both the Canadiens and Avalanche.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/33_patrick_roy.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Patrick_Roy</link>
</player>

<player id="34">
<jersey>34</jersey>
<name>John Vanbiesbrouck</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Having his debut with the New York Rangers, Vanbiesbrouck won the Vezina Trophy as the league's top goaltender and was named a First Team NHL All-Star in his second NHL season.</p><p>He joined the Florida Panthers after 11 seasons with the Rangers and was a three-time all-star as well as led the Panthers to their first and only Stanley Cup Finals appearance in 1996.</p><p>While in Florida he recorded his 300th career victory, becoming the 15th and only the second American goaltender in NHL history to do so. During his career, Vanbiesbrouck compiled a record of 374 wins, 346 losses, 119 ties, and 40 shutouts, making him the winningest American-born goaltender.</p><p>He was inducted into the United States Hockey Hall of Fame in 2007.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/34_john_vanbiesbrouck.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Vanbiesbrouck</link>
</player>

<player id="35">
<jersey>35</jersey>
<name>Tony Esposito</name>
<bio><![CDATA[<p>Esposito was the first NHL Goalie to officially wear the number 35, a common number now worn by many Goaltenders. It was assigned to him during training camp prior to the Chicago Black Hawks 1969-'70 season as the standard numbers 1 and 30 were already assigned. After posting a shutout in his first ever exhibition game for the Hawks, he chose to keep wearing the number.</p><p>During that season Esposito posted a 2.17 GAA and setting a modern day NHL record with fifteen shutouts, for which he won the Calder Trophy as the league's best rookie. He also took the Vezina Trophy and was named to the First All-Star team at season's end. He also was runner-up for league MVP (Hart Trophy). It was during this record setting season he earned the nickname Tony 'O' for his shutout abilities.</p><p>His number 35 was retired by the Blackhawks on November 20, 1988.</p>]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/35_tony_esposito.jpg</photo>
<link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tony_Esposito</link>
</player>

<player id="36">
<jersey>36</jersey>
<name>null</name>
<bio><![CDATA[null]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/.jpg</photo>
<link>null</link>
</player>

<player id="37">
<jersey>37</jersey>
<name>null</name>
<bio><![CDATA[null]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/.jpg</photo>
<link>null</link>
</player>

<player id="38">
<jersey>38</jersey>
<name>null</name>
<bio><![CDATA[null]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/.jpg</photo>
<link>null</link>
</player>

<player id="39">
<jersey>39</jersey>
<name>Dominik Hasek</name>
<bio><![CDATA[null]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/dominik_hasek.jpg</photo>
<link>null</link>
</player>

<player id="40">
<jersey>40</jersey>
<name>Henrik Zetterberg</name>
<bio><![CDATA[null]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/henrik_zetterberg.jpg</photo>
<link>null</link>
</player>

<player id="41">
<jersey>41</jersey>
<name>null</name>
<bio><![CDATA[d]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/34 .jpg</photo>
<link>d</link>
</player>

<player id="42">
<jersey>42</jersey>
<name>null</name>
<bio><![CDATA[null]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/35 .jpg</photo>
<link>null</link>
</player>

<player id="43">
<jersey>43</jersey>
<name>null</name>
<bio><![CDATA[null]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/.jpg</photo>
<link>null</link>
</player>

<player id="44">
<jersey>44</jersey>
<name>null</name>
<bio><![CDATA[null]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/.jpg</photo>
<link>null</link>
</player>

<player id="45">
<jersey>45</jersey>
<name>null</name>
<bio><![CDATA[null]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/.jpg</photo>
<link>null</link>
</player>

<player id="46">
<jersey>46</jersey>
<name>null</name>
<bio><![CDATA[null]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/ .jpg</photo>
<link>null</link>
</player>

<player id="47">
<jersey>47</jersey>
<name>null</name>
<bio><![CDATA[null]]></bio>
<photo>faces/lookup/ .jpg</photo>
<link>null</link>
</player>

</hockeyPlayers>